<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Am I fat or what?</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Enter your name</string>
    <string name="missing_name">Missing a name</string>
    <string name="radio_male">Male</string>
    <string name="radio_female">Female</string>
    <string name="text_gender">State your biological gender</string>
    <string name="bad_habits">Please choose as many of your bad habits as you can identify from the following:</string>
    <string name="sleeping">Sleeping irregular times or less than 6 hours/day</string>
    <string name="smoking">Smoking</string>
    <string name="drinking">Drinking Alcohol (more than 2 measures/week)</string>
    <string name="exercise_text">Choose your level of exercise</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_0">I\'m a couch potato</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_1">I walk occasionally</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_2">I walk regularly, prefer to climb stairs</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_3">I use the gym 1&#8211;2 times/week</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_4">I use the gym more than 3 times/week</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_0_outcome">Try to get outside and walk sometimes, you might like it!</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_1_outcome">Consider doing more physical activities than just a walk. Climb stairs, run, climb a mountain. Get comfortable shoes, it might help.</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_2_outcome">You are already doing a good job, physical activities are great. Try getting a bicycle, or consider having morning runs. They are refreshing.</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_3_outcome">Going to a gym is good, but don\'t forget to have real physical activities as well, walk and run outside, cycle or swim.</string>
    <string name="exercise_level_4_outcome">Gyms are great but fresh air is better. Try to train in nature if possible. Jog, run, swim, go skiing, you\'ll enjoy it more!</string>
    <string name="intro_text">This application helps you find your current BMI (Body mass index), and your health condition. It is not a medical device or medical application and should not be used as such.</string>
    <string name="button_reset_ui">Clean data</string>
    <string name="button_calculate">Calculate</string>
    <string name="text_age">"Age: "</string>
    <string name="text_height">"Height (cm): "</string>
    <string name="text_weight">"Weight (Kg): "</string>
    <string name="output_title_gender">"Gender: "</string>
    <string name="output_title_name">"Name: "</string>
    <string name="text_quiz">And a quiz to test your health and fitness knowledge</string>
    <string name="text_physical">It\'s best to exercise in physical ways, walk more, climb stairs, run instead of always using your car, elevators, automated tools and a gym. </string>
    <string name="radio_correct">Correct</string>
    <string name="radio_wrong">Wrong</string>
    <string name="text_physical_answer">Doing all physical activities using your own strength is a way of life and helps you keep healthy even when you\'re not using a gym. You are exercising 7 days a week, in contrary to using a gym, where you might skip some days, or even weeks if you're on vacation or sick at home.</string>
    <string name="text_extreme_training">You want to take part to a marathon or some other extreme athletic activity. What should you do? (Check as many as you think)</string>
    <string name="check_training">Do some heavy daily training</string>
    <string name="check_doctor">Get a checkup and see if you are in a condition that allows you to take part on the athletic event</string>
    <string name="check_eat_healthy">Start a healthy diet</string>
    <string name="text_discomfort">During your training you get dizzy, what would you do?</string>
    <string name="radio_stop">Stop for 5 minutes and continue later</string>
    <string name="radio_doctor">Consult a doctor or your training instructor</string>
    <string name="button_check_quiz">Check quiz answers</string>
    <string name="button_clean_quiz">Reset quiz</string>
    <string name="bmi_outcome_title">Your BMI and outcome:</string>
    <string name="bmi_outcome_text">Please fill in your details and hit the Calculate button</string>
    <string name="outcome_correct">Please read the outcome and correct the invalid values</string>
    <string name="age_values_accepted">Age should be between 1 and 99</string>
    <string name="height_values_accepted">Enter height between 150 and 215 cm</string>
    <string name="weight_values_accepted">Enter weight between 45 and 99</string>
    <string name="bmi_15">you are severely underweight, consult a doctor immediately.</string>
    <string name="bmi_19">you should eat more, you are underweight.</string>
    <string name="bmi_25">you weight exactly as much as you should. Good job!</string>
    <string name="bmi_30">you are slightly overweight. In other words you\'re a little bit fat. Exercise more or eat less.</string>
    <string name="bmi_35">you clearly need diet and exercise. Your BMI result yields Obese.</string>
    <string name="bmi_over">your health could be at risk. You should see a doctor.</string>
    <string name="bmi_error">BMI error.</string>
    <string name="bad_habits_smoking_outcome">Smoking is bad for your health, shortens your breath, makes you get tired more easily.</string>
    <string name="bad_habits_drinking_outcome">Drinking is bad for your kidneys, and athlets should have good kidneys.</string>
    <string name="bad_habits_sleeping_outcome">Sleeping less than normal or irregularly could exhaust your body and heart.</string>
    <string name="bad_habits_none_outcome">You don\'t have any habits that could damage your heart or kidneys, good job!</string>
    <string name="outcome_bmi_title">"Your BMI is "</string>
    <string name="your_score_is">"Your score is "</string>
    <string name="out_of_three">" out of 3"</string>
    <string name="complete_the_quiz">Please complete the quiz before hitting that button!</string>
</resources>
